Chen Fei, cheer up.
تشن فاي ، ابتهج.
No one has hit you yet.
لم يضربك أحد حتى الآن.
You got down.
نزلت.
It's no big deal.
ليس بالأمر الجلل.
Or you can start again.
أو يمكنك البدء من جديد.
You're so beautiful. What are you afraid of?
ًأنت جميلة جدا.  من ماذا انت خائف؟
I'm afraid
أنا خائف
I'm afraid that without money,
أخشى أنه بدون نقود ،
Without a job,
بدون وظيفة،
No one loves you.
لا أحد يحبك.
ILOVEYOU
انا احبك
You have no money and no job.
ليس لديك مال ولا وظيفة.
I raised you.
لقد ربيتك.
I'll sign the contract with Rui Qi tomorrow.
سأوقع العقد مع روي تشي غدًا.
I'll raise you from now on.
سأرفعك من الآن فصاعدا.
When the sky falls, I will be there.
عندما تسقط السماء ، سأكون هناك.
It's okay.
حسنا.
Fortunately, I have you by my side.
لحسن الحظ ، أنا بجانبي.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have known.
وإلا لما عرفت.
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Don't be afraid. It's okay.
لا تخافوا.  حسنا.
You have me, I'll protect you.
لديك أنا ، سأحميك.
I will never leave you.
لن أتركك أبدا.
That's it.
هذا هو.
How's it going?
كيف تجري الامور؟
And fell asleep.
وسقطت نائما.
Go back first.
العودة أولا.
I'll stay here with her.
سأبقى هنا معها.
good
جيد
Take care of her first.
اعتني بها أولا.
Call me if you need help.
اتصل بي إذا كنت بحاجة إلى مساعدة.
I'll be right there.
سأكون هناك.
I just finished shooting.
لقد انتهيت للتو من التصوير.
He's downstairs at Phil's.
إنه في الطابق السفلي عند فيل.
How's Phil?
كيف حال فيل؟
Actually, it's not good.
في الواقع ، هذا ليس جيدًا.
Phil has always cared.
لطالما اهتم فيل.
Her past
ماضيها
Now it's been exposed online.
الآن تم الكشف عنها عبر الإنترنت.
It's the same as
إنها نفس ملفات
The deepest secret.
أعمق سر.
I was actually very scared.
كنت في الواقع خائفة جدا.
She's upset.
إنها مستاءة.
I'm afraid she can't accept it.
أخشى أنها لا تستطيع قبول ذلك.
Who I used to be.
من اعتدت ان اكون
But I dare not show fear.
لكني لا أجرؤ على إظهار الخوف.
Because if you don't
لأنه إذا لم تفعل
If you are scared,
إذا كنت خائفة ،
She has no one to rely on.
ليس لديها من تعتمد عليه.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
She will survive.
سوف تنجو.
Everyone has scars in their hearts.
كل شخص لديه ندوب في قلوبهم.
It's not that easy.
الأمر ليس بهذه السهولة.
At least Phyl has you.
على الأقل لديك فيل.
Psychologically speaking,
من الناحية النفسية ،
People can be vulnerable all their lives.
يمكن أن يكون الناس عرضة للخطر طوال حياتهم.
Can also be strong.
يمكن أن تكون قوية أيضًا.
My heart was broken.
تحطم قلبي.
Can be rebuilt.
يمكن إعادة بنائها.
So you don't have to be too pessimistic.
لذلك ليس عليك أن تكون متشائمًا جدًا.
But even if it is rebuilt,
ولكن حتى لو أعيد بناؤها ،
The cracks on it
الشقوق الموجودة عليه
Can't be erased.
لا يمكن محوها.
If a man
إذا كان رجلا
It's inevitable that it will be broken.
من المحتم أن يتم كسرها.
In my lifetime,
في حياتي،
Have to experience it once.
يجب أن تجربها مرة واحدة.
Or broken many times.
أو كسر عدة مرات.
You can't protect Phyl.
لا يمكنك حماية فيل.
a lifetime
حياة
Phil needs to be rebuilt.
فيل يحتاج إلى إعادة بناء.
and
و
Was only broken.
تم كسره فقط.
I really understand.
أنا أفهم حقًا.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Let's go.
لنذهب.
I'll take you home.
سوف آخذك للمنزل.
Mr. Zhao.
السيد تشاو.
Xiao Wu.
شياو وو.
Prepare the contract.
تحضير العقد.
Let's sign a contract with Star Entertainment.
دعنا نوقع عقدًا مع Star Entertainment.
Take a look at this.
تفقد هذا.
This is President Shen.
هذا هو الرئيس شين.
Sent it personally.
أرسلها شخصيًا.
Why haven't you come yet?
لماذا لم تأت بعد؟
Mr. Zhao.
السيد تشاو.
If you come,
إذا كنت تأتي،
We can sign the contract.
يمكننا توقيع العقد.
There's something wrong with the contract.
هناك شيء خاطئ في العقد.
I can't sign it today.
لا يمكنني التوقيع عليه اليوم.
The details
التفاصيل
Is there any problem?
هل هناك اي مشكلة؟
It's not about the details.
لا يتعلق الأمر بالتفاصيل.
But
ولكن
Sorry, Mr. Zhao.
آسف يا سيد تشاو.
I'm late.
أنا متأخر.
I signed the contract with Mr. Zhao today.
لقد وقعت العقد مع السيد Zhao اليوم.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Mr. Zhao hasn't told you?
لم يخبرك السيد تشاو؟
The Ruiqi Group has decided
قررت مجموعة رويقي
And use Zihao to make them.
واستخدم Zihao لصنعها.
The spokesman.
المتحدث.
Star has been replaced.
تم استبدال النجمة.
Is it true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Really
حقًا
I'll explain to you later.
سأشرح لك لاحقًا.
Mr. Zhao.
السيد تشاو.
Let's put the contract
دعونا نضع العقد
Let's talk about it.
دعنا نتحدث عن ذلك.
People who have nothing to do with it can go out first.
يمكن للأشخاص الذين لا علاقة لهم به الخروج أولاً.
sorry
آسف
I'm not in the mood.
أنا لست في مزاج جيد.
Another day.
يوم آخر.
OK
نعم
Thousand yarn.
ألف غزل.
Come out with me.
تعال معي.
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
We used all the means.
استخدمنا كل الوسائل.
But I didn't get it.
لكني لم أفهم.
Endorsement contract
عقد التظهير
It seems that the world
يبدو أن العالم
It's still fair.
لا يزال هذا عادلاً.
Whose is it?
لمن هو؟
Who will get it back?
من سيستعيدها؟
If you're a male,
إذا كنت ذكرا ،
Disappointed?
خائب الامل؟
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I have long expected that
لقد توقعت ذلك منذ فترة طويلة
There's nothing to be disappointed about.
لا يوجد ما يخيب أمله.
Look at that pair of yours.
انظر إلى هذا الزوج الخاص بك.
You are so proud of yourself.
أنت فخور بنفسك.
It matches the ambition of a young man.
يطابق طموح الشاب.
This sentence
هذه الجملة
Who are you talking about?
عن من تتكلم؟
why
لماذا
Why did you let President Shen
لماذا تركت الرئيس شين
To oppose STAR being the spokesman.
أن يعارض ستار كونه المتحدث الرسمي.
I don't think Star is suitable.
لا أعتقد أن ستار مناسب.
You think it's inappropriate?
هل تعتقد أنه غير مناسب؟
What makes you think it's inappropriate?
ما الذي يجعلك تعتقد أنه غير لائق؟
Don't you like Star?
ألا تحب ستار؟
Why did you ruin it?
لماذا دمرتها؟
This is my chance.
هذه فرصتي.
I didn't mean to ruin him.
لم أقصد تدميره.
I just want Star to be an actress.
أريد فقط أن تكون النجمة ممثلة.
I'm worried about him and Rui Qi.
أنا قلق عليه و روي تشي.
After signing the contract,
بعد توقيع العقد ،
Will be bound by a treaty, right?
سوف تلتزم بمعاهدة ، أليس كذلك؟
Then he can only be a singer.
ثم يمكنه فقط أن يكون مغنيًا.
Who told you about this contract?
من أخبرك عن هذا العقد؟
Will tie him down.
سوف يقيده.
Tong Tong said that.
قال تونغ تونغ ذلك.
I read it myself.
قرأته بنفسي.
It's clearly written on it.
من الواضح أنه مكتوب عليها.
The treaty states that Star must
تنص المعاهدة على أنه يجب على ستار
To complete Rui Qi's arrangement.
لإكمال ترتيب روي تشي.
That was the previous contract.
كان هذا هو العقد السابق.
your daughter
ابنتك
Please take a look.
من فضلك الق نظرة.
Is this a new one?
هل هذا جديد؟
Before that, Ruonan and I
قبل ذلك ، أنا ورونان
We have reached an agreement.
لقد توصلنا إلى اتفاق.
As an actress,
كممثلة
To sign the contract with Ruiqi Group.
توقيع العقد مع مجموعة رويقي.
Spokesman
المتحدث الرسمي
We're even willing to
نحن على استعداد لذلك
To match Star's schedule.
لتتناسب مع جدول ستار.
To adjust the performance.
لضبط الأداء.
And the activity time.
ووقت النشاط.
Do you know?
هل تعرف؟
This contract is very important
هذا العقد مهم جدا
How important is it?
ما هي أهميتها؟
He's not a singer now, but an actor.
إنه ليس مغنيًا الآن ، لكنه ممثل.
The corresponding exposure rate
معدل التعرض المقابل
His business value
قيمة عمله
Will fall rapidly.
سوف تسقط بسرعة.
But with this contract,
لكن مع هذا العقد ،
Can not only make him
لا يمكن أن تجعله فقط
To get more resources.
للحصول على المزيد من الموارد.
Better resources.
موارد أفضل.
It can even bring more.
يمكن أن تجلب المزيد.
A job opportunity, Miss.
فرصة عمل يا آنسة.
It cost me and Ruonan.
كلفني ذلك ورونان.
So strong.
قوي جدا.
It was finally cleared.
تم تطهيره أخيرًا.
All the obstacles
كل العقبات
It's fine now.
كل شيء على ما يرام الآن.
You ruined everything.
أنت خربت كل شيء.
impossible
غير ممكن
Dugu Ruoruo, how could she?
دوجو رورو ، كيف يمكنها ذلك؟
Why would you support Star?
لماذا تدعم ستار؟
Is that right?
هل هذا صحيح؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
You underestimated Ruuo's courage.
لقد قللت من شأن شجاعة Ruuo.
before that
قبل ذلك
In order to support Star as an actress,
من أجل دعم ستار كممثلة ،
Even prepared.
حتى على استعداد.
To give up the contract.
للتخلي عن العقد.
But you.
لكنك.
Your selfishness
أنانيتك
Your impulse, your naivety.
دافعك ، سذاجتك.
Your self-righteousness
برك الذاتي
And made Star lose
وجعل النجم يخسر
This is a good chance.
هذه فرصة جيدة.
Thousand yarn.
ألف غزل.
If you love someone,
إذا كنت تحب شخصا ما،
To help him.
لكي نساعده.
Let him be.
دعه يكون.
Instead of causing him trouble.
بدلا من أن يسبب له المتاعب.
What should we do?
ماذا علينا ان نفعل؟
Then I'm...
ثم أنا...
I'm calling now.
أنا أتصل الآن.
Give it to my dad.
أعطها لأبي.
I asked him to change Star back.
طلبت منه تغيير ستار مرة أخرى.
It's too late.
لقد فات الأوان.
You've managed to get your father
لقد تمكنت من الحصول على والدك
And made a decision.
واتخذوا قرارا.
And as him,
وكما هو ،
The decision he made
القرار الذي اتخذه
Can't be changed at will.
لا يمكن تغييرها في الإرادة.
therefore
وبالتالي
Sida
سيدا
You are doomed to lose this chance.
أنت محكوم عليك أن تفقد هذه الفرصة.
It's all my fault.
هذا كله خطأي.
The headquarters came to inform us.
جاء المقر لإبلاغنا.
I can't control it.
لا أستطيع السيطرة عليه.
I understand.
أفهم.
You also said that
انت ايضا قلت ذلك
The contract is selfish.
العقد أناني.
Actually, in my heart,
في الواقع ، في قلبي ،
I can't bear it.
لا أستطيع تحمل ذلك.
Now the back door
الآن الباب الخلفي
But he didn't leave.
لكنه لم يغادر.
I'm more down-to-earth.
أنا أكثر واقعية.
I can't.
لا أستطبع.
And become a spokesman.
ويصبح ناطقًا رسميًا.
He's not strong enough.
إنه ليس قويا بما فيه الكفاية.
After that, it will be better.
بعد ذلك سيكون أفضل.
We have many chances to cooperate.
لدينا فرص كثيرة للتعاون.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
I'm very happy.
انا سعيد جدا.
Because you understand me.
لأنك تفهمني.
It's not my fault.
ليس خطئي.
But at the same time, I was sad.
لكن في نفس الوقت كنت حزينا.
Because you still won't accept it.
لأنك ما زلت لا تقبله.
My selfish.
أناني.
I forgot to ask you.
لقد نسيت ان اسألك.
Your friend's...
صديقك ...
Phil!
فيل!
Yes
نعم
she
هي
Is she alright?
هل هي بخير؟
Correct!
صحيح!
I'm going back to see her.
سأعود لرؤيتها.
I can give it to you.
أستطيع أن أعطيها لك.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I'll go myself.
سأذهب بنفسي.
Bye
وداعا
Qian Sha, what's wrong with you?
تشيان شا ، ما خطبك؟
Who bullied you?
من تخويفك؟
sorry
آسف
It's all my fault.
هذا كله خطأي.
The endorsement of Rui Qi.
تأييد روي تشي.
Nothing
لا شئ
I just heard that
لقد سمعت ذلك للتو
It's not your fault.
انها ليست غلطتك.
I'm not capable enough.
أنا لست قادرًا بما يكفي.
They wanted to replace me.
أرادوا أن يستبدلي.
For the sake of Ruo.
من أجل Ruo.
To reconsider it.
لإعادة النظر فيه.
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
I have self-knowledge.
لدي معرفة بالنفس.
I'm just worried that
أنا فقط قلق من ذلك
If a man can,
إذا استطاع الرجل ،
Disappointment
خيبة الامل
You really don't blame me?
أنت حقا لا تلومني؟
No
رقم
It's all my fault.
هذا كله خطأي.
Call my dad.
اتصل بوالدي.
I want to change you.
اريد ان اغيرك
I thought that
وأعتقد أن
You can be an actor.
يمكنك أن تكون ممثلا.
You have no constraints.
ليس لديك قيود.
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
It's not your fault.
انها ليست غلطتك.
I have to blame myself.
علي أن ألوم نفسي.
I'm not strong enough.
لست قوي بما فيه الكفاية.
Not good enough.
ليس جيدا بما فيه الكفاية.
Besides,
بجانب،
I have to thank you.
علي أن أشكرك.
Without your encouragement,
بدون تشجيعك
I didn't have the courage to tell Sister Ruo.
لم يكن لدي الشجاعة لأخبر الأخت رو.
I want to be an actress.
أريد أن أكون ممثلة.
And she agreed to it.
ووافقت على ذلك.
I'm satisfied.
أنا راضٍ.
Really
حقًا
But obviously,
لكن من الواضح ،
Everyone has worked hard.
لقد عمل الجميع بجد.
That's a lot.
هذا كثير.
I didn't get
لم احصل
It means it doesn't belong to me.
هذا يعني أنه لا يخصني.
When I grow stronger one day,
عندما تزداد قوة يومًا ما ،
Excellent.
ممتاز.
It will come back.
سوف يعود.
And I have nothing now.
وليس لدي أي شيء الآن.
You're so relaxed.
أنت مرتاح جدا.
I can chase it with all my might.
يمكنني مطاردتها بكل قوتي.
My dream of acting.
حلمي بالتمثيل.
Let the past be the past.
دع الماضي يكون الماضي.
The future is the most important.
المستقبل هو الأهم.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Sida
سيدا
What's up
ما أخبارك
Why are you so nice?
لماذا انت لطيف جدا
I did something wrong.
لقد فعلت شيئا خاطئا.
Nothing
لا شئ
You comforted me in return.
في المقابل أراحتني.
Thousand yarn.
ألف غزل.
Speak nicely.
تحدث بلطف.
No, no. Don't touch it.
لا لا.  لا تلمسه.
Thousand yarn.
ألف غزل.
Thank you, Star.
شكرا لك يا ستار.
Give me a hug.
احضني.
You have no idea how much I blame myself.
ليس لديك فكرة كم ألوم نفسي.
Qian Sha, I can't breathe.
Qian Sha، I can't breathe. تشيان شا ، لا أستطيع التنفس.
Give me a hug.
احضني.
No, no. I can't.
لا لا.  لا أستطبع.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Si Da, you're so kind.
سي دا ، أنت لطيف جدًا.
Are you a male sister?
هل أنت أخت ذكر؟
Phil is in big trouble this time.
فيل في ورطة كبيرة هذه المرة.
Many partners have terminated.
تم إنهاء العديد من الشركاء.
The cooperation with Phil.
التعاون مع فيل.
Even the wing fashion
حتى أزياء الجناح
To replace Phil.
ليحل محل فيل.
Please help her.
الرجاء مساعدتها.
Don't tell her about this.
لا تخبرها عن هذا.
She has no choice now.
ليس لديها خيار الآن.
To be irritated.
ليغضب.
I'll handle it.
أنا التعامل معها.
good
جيد
You want to replace Phyl?
تريد استبدال فيل؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Phyl, she has been
فيل ، لقد كانت
It's really not easy.
إنه ليس بالأمر السهل حقًا.
There are many manufacturers
هناك العديد من الشركات المصنعة
To replace her.
ليحل محلها.
I...
أنا...
I want to ask you a favor.
اريد ان اطلب منك خدمة.
Even if you reject me,
حتى لو رفضتني
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
Because I can understand
لأنني أستطيع أن أفهم
You have your own position.
لديك منصبك الخاص.
I promise you,
أعدك،
What did you promise me?
ماذا وعدتني؟
Do your best to keep Phyl's endorsement.
ابذل قصارى جهدك للحفاظ على تأييد Phyl.
I didn't plan to
لم أخطط لذلك
Replace Phil.
استبدل فيل.
Although there are many people inside,
على الرغم من وجود العديد من الأشخاص في الداخل ،
The voices of doubt.
اصوات الشك.
But I believe I can solve it.
لكنني أعتقد أنني أستطيع حلها.
And I know
وأنا أعرف
Phyl is your good friend.
فيل هو صديقك المقرب.
I know what she means to you.
أنا أعرف ما تعنيه لك.
I promised you.
انا وعدتك.
I will definitely make it.
سأفعلها بالتأكيد.
And you said that
وأنت قلت ذلك
There's nothing I can't solve.
لا يوجد شيء لا أستطيع حله.
The problem?
المشكلة؟
I'm relieved.
أنا مرتاح.
What about Phil?
ماذا عن فيل؟
Please.
لو سمحت.
You should have a lot of things.
يجب أن يكون لديك الكثير من الأشياء.
Are you busy?
هل أنت مشغول؟
I won't bother you.
لن ازعجك.
to wait a moment
انتظر لحظة
You and Zhao Yucheng
أنت و Zhao Yucheng
What's the progress?
ما هو التقدم؟
Why are you asking about Zhao Yusheng?
لماذا تسأل عن Zhao Yusheng؟
Are you still jealous?
هل مازلت غيور؟
I'm just asking.
انا اسالك فقط.
You're just jealous.
إنك فقط غيور.
I'm jealous.
أنا غيور.
Why should I be jealous?
لماذا يجب أن أغار؟
There's a way to make you
هناك طريقة لجعلك
You are openly jealous.
أنت غيور بشكل علني.
Do you want to know?
هل تريد أن تعرف؟
What?
ماذا؟
Be my man.
كن رجلي.
Are you kidding me?
هل تمزح معي؟
I'm serious.
أنا جادة.
You look jealous.
تبدو غيورًا.
So cute.
جميل جدا.
I'm not jealous.
أنا لست غيورًا.
I'm no better than Zhao Yucheng.
أنا لست أفضل من Zhao Yucheng.
Much better.
أفضل بكثير.
I'm more confident than him.
أنا أكثر ثقة منه.
I'm so confident.
أنا واثق جدًا.
From your micro expression,
من تعبيرك الجزئي ،
I saw the tension, fear and guilty.
رأيت التوتر والخوف والذنب.
When I approached you just now,
عندما اقتربت منك الآن ،
You're the only one
أنت الوحيد
A defensive posture.
موقف دفاعي.
It shows your heart.
يظهر قلبك.
Very nervous.
متوتر جدا.
Because you don't know.
لأنك لا تعرف.
How to respond to my request.
كيف ترد على طلبي.
You just explained that
لقد أوضحت ذلك للتو
You don't have a jealous look.
ليس لديك نظرة غيورة.
His eyes suddenly went up.
ارتفعت عيناه فجأة.
Rapid breathing.
تنفس سريع.
It means you are guilty.
هذا يعني أنك مذنب.
Are you nervous?
هل انت متوتر؟
Of course, it's possible that I'm guilty.
بالطبع ، من المحتمل أنني مذنب.
The act of being jealous.
فعل الغيرة.
It's also possible that
من الممكن أيضًا أن
Care about someone very much.
يهتم بشخص ما كثيرا.
Right?
حق؟
Don't mention it.
لا تذكرها.
Because from your micro expression,
لأنه من خلال تعبيرك الجزئي ،
I have the answer.
لدي الجواب.
A little facial expression.
القليل من تعبيرات الوجه.
Who wouldn't?
من منا لا؟
Dugu is like a man.
المدينة مثل الرجل.
I shouldn't have
لا يجب أن أمتلك
Microfacial psychology taught you
علمك علم النفس الدقيق للوجه
I was almost caught.
لقد تم القبض علي تقريبا.
Are you awake?
هل انت مستيقظ؟
It's good to wake up.
من الجيد أن تستيقظ.
Come on.
هيا.
I bought it for you.
لقد اشتريتها لك.
Your favorite pig's trotter.
هرول الخنزير المفضل لديك.
Eat it while it's hot.
تناولها وهي ساخنة.
Do you think I'm
هل تعتقد أنني
Are you still in the mood to eat?
هل مازلت في مزاج تأكل؟
Then stop eating.
ثم توقف عن الأكل.
You have to stay in shape.
عليك أن تحافظ على لياقتك.
To take photos.
لالتقاط الصور.
What photo?
ما الصورة؟
No one dares to use me now.
لا أحد يجرؤ على استخدامي الآن.
I was abandoned by everyone.
لقد هجرني الجميع.
No,
رقم،
Wing Fashion didn't abandon you.
أزياء وينج لم تتخلى عنك.
Ji Mo also asked me to tell you that
طلب مني جي مو أيضًا أن أخبرك بذلك
To take photos tomorrow.
لالتقاط الصور غدا.
How do you know?
كيف علمت بذلك؟
You went to intercede with Ji Mo?
هل ذهبت للتوسط مع جي مو؟
I just ran into him.
لقد صادفته للتو.
I knew it.
كنت أعرف.
If you hadn't gone to him,
إذا لم تكن قد ذهبت إليه ،
To intercede,
للتشفع ،
He probably wouldn't dare to use me.
ربما لن يجرؤ على استخدامي.
Yes
نعم
I went to see Zimmer.
ذهبت لرؤية زيمر.
But he also said
لكنه قال أيضا
He didn't want to replace you.
لم يكن يريد أن يحل محلك.
You're very popular now.
أنت مشهور جدًا الآن.
Don't be so pessimistic.
لا تكن متشائما جدا.
I don't need your pity.
لست بحاجة لشفقتك.
And pitiful.
ومثير للشفقة.
I didn't pity you.
أنا لم أشفق عليك.
Don't pretend to be
لا تتظاهر
As the savior, okay?
كمنقذ ، اتفقنا؟
It's annoying.
انه مزعج.
Chen Fei.
تشن فاي.
I'm talking to you nicely.
أنا أتحدث إليكم بلطف.
You won't listen. Are you looking for a scolding?
لن تستمع.  هل تبحث عن توبيخ؟
For you,
لك،
Running around.
يدور حول.
I just finished a meeting.
لقد انتهيت للتو من الاجتماع.
I will come to your home to look for you.
سوف آتي إلى منزلك للبحث عنك.
When I came to your house,
عندما أتيت إلى منزلك ،
I got another call from Xiao Xiao.
تلقيت مكالمة أخرى من شياو شياو.
I went to Wing Fashion.
ذهبت إلى Wing Fashion.
I have to coax you back.
يجب أن أقنعك بالعودة.
What's my intention?
ما هي نيتي؟
I didn't mean to make you happy.
لم أقصد أن أجعلك سعيدا.
Don't feel wronged.
لا تشعر بالظلم.
The whole world owes you.
العالم كله مدين لك.
When I was wronged,
عندما ظلمت ،
Have I called you?
هل اتصلت بك
Is there
هل هناك
Nothing.
لا شئ.
I didn't want you to worry.
لا أريدك أن تقلق.
Do you like pig's trotter?
هل تحب خنزير الخنزير؟
It's up to you.
الأمر متروك لك.
Stand still. Don't move.
تراوح مكانها.  .لا تتحرك
If it's a bad guy,
إذا كان شخصًا سيئًا ،
I'll throw him out.
سوف أرميها خارجا.
I've checked everything.
لقد راجعت كل شيء.
There's no danger.
لا يوجد خطر.
There's no explosives.
لا يوجد متفجرات.
A fan's letter to you.
رسالة من المعجبين لك.
And a ball for what?
وكرة من اجل ماذا؟
I have no idea
ليس لدي أي فكرة
Beautiful Phyl.
جميل فيل.
I sent you a pressure ball.
لقد أرسلت لك كرة ضغط.
When you're feeling stressed,
عندما تشعر بالتوتر ،
Or unhappy,
أو غير سعيد ،
Hold it tightly in your hand.
امسكها بإحكام في يدك.
It can relieve the pressure.
يمكن أن يخفف الضغط.
This pressure ball
كرة الضغط هذه
No matter how you shape it,
بغض النظر عن كيفية تشكيله ،
It will return to its original condition.
ستعود إلى حالتها الأصلية.
Actually, people are the same.
في الواقع ، الناس متشابهون.
No matter what the pressure is,
بغض النظر عن الضغط ،
Can be changed back to the way it was.
يمكن تغييرها إلى ما كانت عليه.
Or even use force.
أو حتى استخدام القوة.
To create a stronger explosive force.
لخلق قوة متفجرة أقوى.
That's why you bounce back from the bottom.
لهذا السبب ترتد من القاع.
I believe
أعتقد
You can do the same.
يمكنك أن تفعل الشيء نفسه.
remember
تذكر
I will always be your most loyal.
سأكون دائما أكثر ولاء لك.
Little fan.
مروحة صغيرة.
You still smile?
مازلت تبتسم؟
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
That
الذي - التي
pig trotters
كوارع الخنازير
Come and eat.
تعال و كل.
Luckily, I didn't eat it.
لحسن الحظ ، لم آكله.
That's what women do.
هذا ما تفعله النساء.
Pretentious and hypocritical.
طائش ومنافق.
Should I do it?
هل يلزم أن أفعل ذلك؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Learn from me.
تعلم مني.
Okay, I'm pissed off.
حسنًا ، أنا غاضب.
Don't be angry.
لا تغضب.
Eat pig's feet.
أكل أقدام الخنازير.
pig trotters
كوارع الخنازير
It's not cut.
لا تقطع.
I'll eat whatever I want.
سوف آكل ما أريد.
Didn't you cut it?
ألم تقطعها؟
I'll cut it for you.
سأقطعها لك.
to do sth more quickly
للقيام بالكثير بسرعة أكبر
Alright.
على ما يرام.
do
فعل
I owe you a scolding.
أنا مدين لك بتوبيخ.
who
منظمة الصحة العالمية
Who is it?
من هذا؟
If a man
إذا كان رجلا
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I just woke up.
استيقظت للتو.
I haven't washed yet.
لم اغتسل بعد.
I don't want to
لا اريد
For others to see.
ليراها الآخرون.
Especially you.
خصوصا أنت.
It's not like I haven't seen it before.
ليس الأمر كما لو أنني لم أره من قبل.
It's 9: 30.
إنها 9:30.
I have a meeting at 10: 00.
لدي اجتماع في 10:00.
From here to the office,
من هنا إلى المكتب
It takes 25 minutes.
يستغرق 25 دقيقة.
So I only have five minutes.
لذلك لدي خمس دقائق فقط.
I need to get along with you.
أنا بحاجة إلى التوافق معك.
These five minutes,
هذه الخمس دقائق ،
To support my day.
لدعم يومي.
but
لكن
Five minutes is not enough.
خمس دقائق لا تكفي.
I want you to
أريد منك أن
Every minute with me,
كل دقيقة معي
If a man
إذا كان رجلا
I admit I was a jerk.
أعترف أنني كنت أحمق.
There are too many concerns.
هناك الكثير من المخاوف.
I won't tell you anything
لن أخبرك بأي شيء
What excuse?
أي عذر؟
But give me a chance.
لكن أعطني فرصة.
No matter now or in the future,
لا يهم الآن أو في المستقبل ،
Let me prove my love for you.
دعني أثبت حبي لك.
I really...
أنا في الحقيقه...
I haven't been in a relationship for a long time.
لم أقم بعلاقة منذ فترة طويلة.
I haven't pursued anyone for a long time.
لم أطارد أي شخص منذ فترة طويلة.
I have forgotten
لقد نسيت
The skills of love.
مهارات الحب.
I won't.
أنا لن.
I won't use it on you.
لن أستخدمه عليك.
Any routine.
أي روتين.
So I will try my best.
لذلك سأبذل قصارى جهدي.
To give you security.
لأمنحك الأمن.
I really don't want to miss it again.
أنا حقا لا أريد أن أفتقدها مرة أخرى.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
I need to charge it.
أنا بحاجة لشحنها.
That's it.
هذا هو.
Finally.
أخيراً.
I'm going to work.
انا ذاهب للعمل.
You look so beautiful when you just woke up.
تبدين جميلة جدا عندما استيقظت للتو.
If a man
إذا كان رجلا
You just woke up.
لقد استيقظت للتو.
It's so beautiful.
انها جميلة جدا.
Am I beautiful?
هل أنا جميل؟
Do you?
هل أنت؟
This is the legendary natural beauty.
هذا هو الجمال الطبيعي الأسطوري.
Messy beauty, wild beauty.
جمال فوضوي ، جمال بري.
Why am I beautiful? I'm so beautiful.
لماذا انا جميلة  انا جميل جدا.
Too beautiful is a burden.
جميل جدا هو عبء.
To keep a low profile.
للحفاظ على الانظار.
You are not allowed to
أنت غير مسموح لك أن
Hello, hello.
أهلا أهلا.
I'm
انا
where
أين
Really?
هل حقا؟
Yes, I have.
نعم لدي.
We have a schedule recently.
لدينا جدول زمني مؤخرًا.
Okay, thank you. Let me know.
حسنا شكرا لك.  اسمحوا لي أن أعرف.
Bye
وداعا
The sun is rising in the west.
تشرق الشمس في الغرب.
sister
أخت
Why are you so happy?
لماذا أنت سعيد جدا؟
It's rare.
هذا نادر.
Have you ever heard of
هل سمعت من قبل عن
Embrace the future.
احتضان المستقبل.
This play
هذه المسرحية
The crew wants you there.
الطاقم يريدك هناك.
Audition Male 2.
ذكر الاختبار 2.
This is the last time
هذه هي المرة الأخيرة
The big red project.
المشروع الأحمر الكبير.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Embrace the future.
احتضان المستقبل.
Qian Sha took a pile of scripts
أخذ Qian Sha كومة من النصوص
That name seems to be it.
يبدو أن هذا الاسم هو.
Song Zihao seems to be a male.
يبدو أن Song Zihao ذكر.
I'd better forget it.
من الأفضل أن أنساه.
So that you don't have to
حتى لا تضطر إلى ذلك
You're always looking up.
أنت دائما تبحث عن.
Do you still want to act?
هل مازلت تريد التمثيل؟
Yes, of course.
نعم بالطبع.
But Song Zihao
لكن سونغ زيهاو
There's no but.
لا يوجد لكن.
A real actor.
ممثل حقيقي.
Won't pick a rival.
لن تختار منافسا.
Are you acting?
هل تتصرف؟
Whether to act with Song Zihao or not.
سواء للعمل مع Song Zihao أم لا.
What does it matter?
ما الدي يهم؟
And a newbie.
ومبتدئ.
It's not your turn to pick and choose.
ليس دورك في الاختيار والاختيار.
Got it, sister.
فهمت يا أختي.
I'm telling you,
أنا أخبرك،
I've studied the script.
لقد درست السيناريو.
The male number two is
الرجل الثاني هو
A rare role.
دور نادر.
Although it looks like
على الرغم من أنها تبدو
There aren't many scenes.
ليس هناك الكثير من المشاهد.
But he's indeed better than the male lead.
لكنه بالفعل أفضل من الرجل البطل.
And become more colorful.
وتصبح أكثر سخونة.
Especially his personal setting.
خاصة وضعه الشخصي.
Plump and solid.
ممتلئ الجسم وصلب.
But also affectionate route.
ولكن أيضا طريق حنون.
The female audience
الجمهور النسائي
Is my favorite.
هو المفضل لدي.
If you act well,
إذا تصرفت بشكل جيد ،
It will be you.
ستكون أنت.
In my acting career,
في مسيرتي التمثيلية ،
A good beginning.
بداية جيدة.
sister
أخت
I didn't expect that
لم أتوقع ذلك
You're so well-researched.
أنت جيد البحث.
Where's my job?
اين وظيفتي
To help you choose a good one.
لمساعدتك في اختيار فكرة جيدة.
The script and the role.
السيناريو والدور.
To make you
لاجعلك
To achieve this role.
لتحقيق هذا الدور.
This role also makes you
هذا الدور يجعلك أيضًا
I've picked a script for you.
لقد اخترت سيناريو لك.
And the character.
والشخصية.
Can I pass the audition?
هل يمكنني اجتياز الاختبار؟
It's up to you.
الأمر متروك لك.
Yes, definitely.
نعم بالتأكيد.
I will try my best.
وسأحاول قصارى جهدي.
Take down the role.
خذ الدور.
I repeat.
أكرر.
You are my girl
أنت فتاتي
Song Zihao, are you sick?
سونغ زهاو ، هل أنت مريض؟
You said you wanted to help me with the drama.
قلت أنك تريد مساعدتي في الدراما.
Why are you sleeping?
لماذا انت نائم؟
You can either put on a poker face
يمكنك إما وضع وجه لعبة البوكر
Or act cool.
أو تصرف بشكل رائع.
After all,
بعد كل شيء،
Similar emotions.
مشاعر مماثلة.
I won't compete with you.
لن أتنافس معك.
You're a layman.
أنت شخص عادي.
There's something wrong with the character.
هناك شيء خاطئ في الشخصية.
Tong Tong is an agent.
تونغ تونغ وكيل.
How did you do that?
كيف فعلت ذلك؟
otherwise
خلاف ذلك
You'll be responsible for me from now on.
ستكون مسؤولاً عني من الآن فصاعدًا.
Choose a role.
اختر دورًا.
I'm just an assistant.
أنا مجرد مساعد.
Other work
عمل اخر
Don't try to push it on me.
لا تحاول الضغط علي.
Zihao
زهاو
The coffee from the director.
القهوة من المخرج.
Thank you. Put it there.
شكرًا لك.  ضعها هناك.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Congratulations.
تهانينا.
I heard there's a new employee in your company.
سمعت أن هناك موظفًا جديدًا في شركتك.
To be the second male in our play.
أن أكون الرجل الثاني في مسرحيتنا.
New people
أناس جدد
Who is it?
من هذا؟
It's called Si.
انها تسمى سي.
Sida
سيدا
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
It's called Si Da.
انها تسمى سي دا.
very good
حسن جدا
If Star can be interviewed,
إذا كان من الممكن مقابلة ستار ،
Wouldn't I be able to
ألن أكون قادرًا على ذلك
I saw him.
رأيته.
This job won't be
لن تكون هذه الوظيفة
It's so boring now.
إنه ممل للغاية الآن.
What do you want to say?
ماذا تريد أن تقول؟
You can speak freely.
يمكنك التحدث بحرية.
The bad reviews we received recently
المراجعات السيئة التي تلقيناها مؤخرًا
And 90 percent of the complaints
و 90 بالمائة من الشكاوى
Are all aimed at the endorser.
كلها تستهدف المصدق.
It's Chen Fei's.
انها تشن فاي.
This is very serious.
هذا خطير جدا.
Has affected
قد اثر
The reputation of our brand
سمعة علامتنا التجارية
Don't watch the old season.
لا تشاهد الموسم القديم.
And you're looking into it.
وأنت تبحث فيه.
The more I look, the worse it is.
كلما نظرت أكثر ، كان الأمر أسوأ.
The worst is us.
الأسوأ هو نحن.
For long-term cooperation.
لتعاون طويل الأمد.
Has started asking us
بدأت تسألنا
To increase the proportion of advance payment.
لزيادة نسبة الدفعة المقدمة.
What does that mean?
ماذا يعني ذلك؟
It means that
هذا يعني انه
Don't you have confidence in the future?
ألا تثق في المستقبل؟
How did that result?
كيف كانت النتيجة؟
Ji, I'm wrong.
جي ، أنا مخطئ.
I think it's because of you.
أعتقد أنه بسببك.
Persist in wilfully and arbitrarily
المثابرة على ذلك عن عمد وتعسفي
You insist on using this.
أنت تصر على استخدام هذا.
What gossip-ridden?
ما هي الثرثرة؟
What Chen Fei?
ما تشن فاي؟
Of course, not only this decision,
بالطبع ، ليس هذا القرار فقط ،
A lot of recent decisions
الكثير من القرارات الأخيرة
Are all inside.
كلها بالداخل.
Before you came,
قبل مجيئك،
All the directors
كل المخرجين
You're breathing.
أنت تتنفس.
On behalf of the board,
نيابة عن مجلس الإدارة ،
I solemnly inform you that
أنا أبلغكم رسميا بذلك
Please cancel it immediately.
من فضلك قم بإلغائها على الفور.
Chen Fei, as our company,
Chen Fei ، كشركتنا ،
The image spokesman's decision.
قرار المتحدث باسم الصورة.
Take this stinking meat from us.
خذ هذا اللحم النتن منا.
Can you peel it?
هل يمكنك تقشيرها؟
What everyone said,
ما قاله الجميع ،
I heard it.
سمعته.
But I can't agree.
لكن لا يمكنني أن أوافق.
Your proposal
اقتراحك
Because I think
لأنني اعتقد
The spokesman event.
حدث المتحدث.
To our company.
لشركتنا.
Will pass soon.
سوف يمر قريبا.
Let me ask you one more thing.
اسمح لي أن أسألك شيئًا آخر.
What makes you so sure?
ما الذي يجعلك على يقين من ذلك؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Based on my understanding of public psychology,
بناءً على فهمي لعلم النفس العام ،
Analysis and understanding
التحليل والفهم
This is the information age.
هذا هو عصر المعلومات.
Once a celebrity is involved in a scandal,
بمجرد تورط أحد المشاهير في فضيحة ،
It will cause the public
سوف يسبب ذلك للجمهور
The carnival of public opinion.
كرنفال الرأي العام.
Prying curiosity.
فضول المتطفلين.
The expression of public opinion
التعبير عن الرأي العام
The superiority of morality.
تفوق الأخلاق.
These are all people
هؤلاء هم كل الناس
Focus on the cause of the scandal.
ركز على سبب الفضيحة.
They are looking for
إنهم يبحثون عن
Immediate compensation
تعويض فوري
And this kind of instant compensation
وهذا النوع من التعويض الفوري
Your memory is short.
ذاكرتك قصيرة.
Which is what psychology says,
وهو ما يقوله علم النفس ،
Short-term memory
ذاكرة قصيرة المدي
Will soon be forgotten.
قريبا سوف تنسى.
So we don't have to
لذلك لا داعي لذلك
For the current public opinion,
للرأي العام الحالي ،
Because of this.
و لهذا.
If you look carefully,
إذا نظرت بعناية ،
You will find that
سوف تجد ذلك
The bad comments against Phyl.
التعليقات السيئة ضد Phyl.
Since the first week of the outbreak,
منذ الأسبوع الأول لتفشي المرض ،
Is the most.
هو الاكثر.
After that, it dropped sharply.
بعد ذلك ، انخفض بشكل حاد.
Now, there are almost none.
الآن ، لا يوجد شيء تقريبًا.
What bad comments?
ما التعليقات السيئة؟
Which means it's consistent with psychology.
مما يعني أنه يتفق مع علم النفس.
The oblivion curve
منحنى النسيان
everybody
الجميع
What do you understand?
ماذا تفهم
Follow them.
اتبعهم.
Nod there.
أومئ برأسك هناك.
Anyway, I didn't understand.
على أي حال ، لم أفهم.
Ji, I beg you.
جي ، أتوسل إليكم.
Don't take these.
لا تأخذ هذه.
The psychology of suspense.
سيكولوجية التشويق.
To fool us.
لخداعنا.
I'm a rude man.
أنا رجل فظ.
I'll admit one thing.
سأعترف بشيء واحد.
No matter what theory you put forward,
بغض النظر عن النظرية التي طرحتها ،
Than a good performance.
من أداء جيد.
Are you right?
هل أنت بخير؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Then tell me what your decision is.
ثم قل لي ما هو قرارك.
It's us.
انه نحن.
All of them.
كلهم.
And the future of wing fashion.
ومستقبل أزياء الجناح.
It's a huge responsibility.
إنها مسؤولية ضخمة.
I strongly disagree.
أنا لا أوافق بشدة.
If you want to
أذا أردت
If you don't do that,
إذا لم تفعل ذلك ،
I can only suspect
لا أستطيع إلا أن أشك
Are you capable of
هل أنت قادر على
And continue to work.
واستمر في العمل.
The president of Wing Fashion.
رئيس Wing Fashion.
If you insist on getting the performance,
إذا كنت تصر على الحصول على الأداء ،
What you said,
ماذا قلت،
Then I assure you,
ثم أؤكد لكم ،
Increase sales within three months
زيادة المبيعات في غضون ثلاثة أشهر
Thirty percent.
ثلاثين في المئة.
If I can't,
إذا لم أستطع ،
And resigned.
واستقال.
No
رقم
Old Wang.
وانغ القديم.
How dare he say that?
كيف يجرؤ على قول ذلك؟
Thirty percent.
ثلاثين في المئة.
good
جيد
Three months.
ثلاثة أشهر.
Just three months.
ثلاثة أشهر فقط.
I will wait and see.
وسوف ننتظر ونرى.
Old Wang, old Prince.
وانغ العجوز ، الأمير العجوز.
Thirty percent for three months.
ثلاثون بالمائة لمدة ثلاثة أشهر.
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
Three months? Did I hear you right?
ثلاثة أشهر؟  هل سمعتك صحيح؟
How is that possible?
كيف يعقل ذلك؟
President Ji, I think you should
الرئيس جي ، أعتقد أنه يجب عليك ذلك
Cancel Phil's endorsement status.
قم بإلغاء حالة تأييد Phil.
Or you'll be the one leaving.
أو ستكون الشخص الذي يغادر.
I promised Ruuo
لقد وعدت Ruuo
You must keep Phyl.
يجب أن تحتفظ بفيل.
You have to keep your word.
عليك أن تحافظ على كلمتك.
If you want too many things,
إذا كنت تريد الكثير من الأشياء ،
You can't promise her everything.
لا يمكنك أن تعدها بكل شيء.
As long as you care about it,
ما دمت تهتم بذلك ،
I will do my best to protect it.
سأبذل قصارى جهدي لحمايته.
The price of love
ثمن الحب
It's too big.
انها كبيرة جدا.
No
رقم
As my assistant,
كمساعد لي ،
Can you speak?
هل يمكن ان نتكلم؟
Don't be so upset.
لا تنزعجوا.
Send the statements of all departments
ارسال كشوفات جميع الاقسام
The details.
التفاصيل.
I'm going to make a plan
سأضع خطة
Detailed plan.
خطة مفصلة.
Document statement financial statements
وثيقة بيان البيانات المالية
It's all here.
كل شيء هنا.
Are you sure you want to finish it?
هل أنت متأكد أنك تريد الانتهاء منه؟
After reading these things,
بعد قراءة هذه الأشياء ،
At least a week.
أسبوع على الأقل.
There's always time.
هناك دائمًا وقت.
So I have to sleep in the office again.
لذلك علي أن أنام في المكتب مرة أخرى.
This is your audition script.
هذا هو نص الاختبار الخاص بك.
I marked the time for you.
لقد حددت الوقت بالنسبة لك.
Hurry up and practice.
أسرع وتدرب.
I've memorized the lines.
لقد حفظت السطور.
We need to figure out
نحن بحاجة لمعرفة
The emotions of the characters in it.
عواطف الشخصيات فيه.
good
جيد
Because of you,
بسببك،
I have the ability to love.
لدي القدرة على الحب.
The love scene.
مشهد الحب.
What's so weird about that?
ما هو الغريب في ذلك؟
The love scene can really test
يمكن أن يختبر مشهد الحب حقًا
Acting skills
مهارات التمثيل
But sister,
لكن اختي
I have heterosexual disorder.
أنا أعاني من اضطراب جنساني.
I'm afraid that
أخشى ذلك
The actress who plays with me.
الممثلة التي تلعب معي.
Let me ask you something.
اسمح لي أن أسألك سؤالا.
You said you wanted to be an actress.
قلت أنك تريد أن تكون ممثلة.
Are you ready?
هل أنت جاهز؟
to be ready
لتكون مستعدا
But I was afraid that I would get sick.
لكني كنت أخشى أن أمرض.
I'll be
سأكون
Since you want to be an actor,
بما أنك تريد أن تكون ممثلًا ،
Then you have to overcome it.
ثم عليك التغلب عليها.
Your own mental disorder.
الاضطراب العقلي الخاص بك.
In your acting career,
في مهنتك التمثيلية ،
We will meet in the future.
سوف نلتقي في المستقبل.
A lot of actresses are acting against you.
الكثير من الممثلات يتصرفن ضدك.
You should recognize
يجب أن تتعرف
And face the reality.
ومواجهة الواقع.
I don't want to
لا اريد
Because of you.
بسببك.
I won't give up.
أنا لن أستسلم.
I will read the script.
سوف أقرأ النص.
And analyze the characters.
وتحليل الشخصيات.
And figure out the characters.
واكتشف الشخصيات.
I'll go back and recite the script.
سأعود وأقرأ النص.
Bye, sister.
وداعا يا اختي.
Because of you.
بسببك.
I experienced it all over again.
لقد اختبرت ذلك من جديد.
Human's complex emotions
عواطف الإنسان المعقدة
But then I realized
لكن بعد ذلك أدركت
Love needs to be responded to.
الحب يحتاج إلى الرد.
to punctuate
إلى علامات الترقيم
But no matter what happens here today,
ولكن بغض النظر عما يحدث هنا اليوم ،
I want to tell you out loud.
اريد ان اقول لك بصوت عال.
I love you
أحبك
It's not right to have no feelings.
ليس من الصواب ألا يكون لديك مشاعر.
ILOVEYOU
انا احبك
What are you laughing at?
على ماذا تضحك؟
What's so funny?
ما المضحك في ذلك؟
good
جيد
But you know I'm hard?
لكنك تعلم أنني صعب؟
Emotion, I know this feeling.
العاطفة ، أعرف هذا الشعور.
Needs to be responded to.
يحتاج إلى الرد عليه.
You know I'm hard.
أنت تعلم أنني صعب.
Most of the time, my efforts
معظم الوقت جهودي
Can't be answered.
لا يمكن الرد.
But no matter what,
لكن مهما حدث ،
Here, I'm going to
هنا ، أنا ذاهب إلى
To tell you that I love you.
لأخبرك أنني أحبك.
Hello, Si Da.
مرحبا سي دا.
Can you help me with the arrangement?
هل يمكنك مساعدتي في الترتيب؟
what
ماذا او ما
To help you with the rehearsal.
لمساعدتك في البروفة.
No, no.
مهووس.
I'm busy now.
أنا مشغول الآن.
Besides, I'm not a director.
علاوة على ذلك ، أنا لست مخرجًا.
How can I help you?
كيف يمكنني مساعدك؟
She asked me to overcome the psychological barrier.
طلبت مني تجاوز الحاجز النفسي.
I thought of you first.
فكرت فيك أولا.
Can you help me?
هل بإمكانك مساعدتي؟
He asked you to call me.
طلب منك الاتصال بي.
No
رقم
But she values it very much.
لكنها تقدره كثيرا.
This chance
هذه الفرصة
I don't want to let her down.
لا أريد أن أخذلها.
Okay, wait for me.
حسنًا ، انتظرني.
I'll be there soon.
سأكون هناك قريبا.
very good
حسن جدا
mother
أم
You're still sitting in the courtyard.
أنت ما زلت جالسًا في الفناء.
In the moonlight,
في ضوء القمر،
Looking at that RV?
تبحث في عربة سكن متنقلة؟
The moon above the elm tree
القمر فوق شجرة الدردار
Sida
سيدا
You must work hard.
يجب أن تعمل بجد.
You must pass the audition.
يجب عليك اجتياز الاختبار.
We will be able to
سنكون قادرين على
We meet every day.
نلتقي كل يوم.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
She's bad-tempered.
إنها مزاجية سيئة.
I didn't see Star inside.
لم أرَ نجمة بالداخل.
Are you practicing?
هل تتدرب؟
If I'm right,
إذا أنا على حق،
You're the one
انت المختار
To get Sida into trouble.
لإيقاع سيدا بالمتاعب.
Than Dugu Ruoruo.
ثان دوجو رورو.
And a powerful woman.
وامرأة قوية.
Shen Qiansha.
شن تشيانشا.
How do you know me?
كيف تعرفني؟
I seem to be in the company.
يبدو أنني في الشركة.
Haven't I seen you before?
ألم اراك من قبل؟
Answer me one question first.
أجبني على سؤال واحد أولاً.
Do you want to see it?
هل تريد ان تراه؟
Is Star rehearsing?
هل ستار يتدرب؟
Of course I want to.
بالطبع أريد أن.
But I'm not qualified.
لكني لست مؤهلا.
Now, I have...
الآن لدي...
Is not his assistant anymore.
لم يعد مساعده.
To meet each other.
لمقابلة بعضنا.
I'm the acting teacher of Star.
أنا مدرس التمثيل في Star.
Hello, hello.
أهلا أهلا.
Would you like me to invite you in?
هل تريد مني أن أدعوك للدخول؟
Yes, I'm willing.
نعم ، أنا على استعداد.
Brother, you're here.
أخي ، أنت هنا.
You're a good friend. I'll come as soon as I tell you.
أنت صديق جيد.  سآتي حالما أخبرك.
Come on. Hurry up.
هيا.  عجلوا.
Teach me this.
علمني هذا.
This one.
هذا.
How to do it?
كيف افعلها؟
I really can't.
أنا حقا لا أستطيع.
Sida
سيدا
Qian Sha, what are you doing there?
تشيان شا ، ماذا تفعل هناك؟
I'm training.
أنا أتدرب.
Don't bother me.
لا تزعجني.
I asked her to come.
طلبت منها أن تأتي.
Not brother.
لا أخي.
Don't you know she's a thunder?
ألا تعلم أنها رعد؟
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I also know that she kissed you.
أنا أعلم أيضًا أنها قبلتك.
And confessed to you, right?
واعترف لك ، أليس كذلك؟
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
The thought of it makes me sick.
التفكير في ذلك يجعلني أشعر بالمرض.
This time,
هذا الوقت،
You want her to help you with the drama.
تريد منها مساعدتك في الدراما.
To compete with her.
للتنافس معها.
Impossible. Absolutely impossible.
غير ممكن.  مستحيل تماما.
I'm willing to act.
أنا على استعداد للعمل.
I don't want to.
لا اريد.
I will.
أنا سوف.
No, no. Don't.
لا لا.  لا.
Sida
سيدا
To cure you,
لشفاءك ،
Heterosexual social disorder
الاضطراب الاجتماعي بين الجنسين
You must have Shen Qiansha's help.
يجب أن تحصل على مساعدة شين تشيانشا.
Combat poison with poison
حارب السم بالسم
Besides,
بجانب،
Aren't you always afraid
ألا تخافين دائمًا
This kind of woman?
هذا النوع من النساء؟
Just right
مجرد حق
If you can overcome it,
إذا تمكنت من التغلب عليها ،
Such an opponent.
مثل هذا الخصم.
In the future,
فى المستقبل،
Which opponent did you meet?
أي خصم قابلته؟
You can handle it well.
يمكنك التعامل معها بشكل جيد.
Brother
أخ
Is there no other way?
اليس هنالك طريقة اخرى؟
Let's change.
دعونا نتغير.
It's really not working.
انها حقا لا تعمل.
If this kind of girl
إذا كان هذا النوع من الفتاة
You can handle it.
يمكنك التعامل معها.
What are you afraid of?
من ماذا انت خائف؟
Okay, don't waste time.
حسنًا ، لا تضيع الوقت.
Let's start.
لنبدأ.
Brother
أخ
Now, Star is heading towards Qiansha.
الآن ، ستار يتجه نحو Qiansha.
Take a step.
اتخذ خطوة.
Qiansha is also heading towards Sida.
كيانشا تتجه أيضا نحو سيدا.
Sida
سيدا
Open your eyes.
افتح عينيك.
During the whole process,
خلال العملية برمتها ،
You must have only Qiansha in your eyes.
يجب أن يكون لديك Qiansha فقط في عينيك.
Even if you have
حتى لو كان لديك
Ten thousand voices.
عشرة آلاف صوت.
To avoid her eyes.
لتجنب عينيها.
You have to break it.
عليك كسرها.
The ten thousand voices
عشرة آلاف صوت
Sida
سيدا
Don't be afraid.
لا تخافوا.
I'm here to help you.
أنا هنا لمساعدتك.
I know you hate me.
انا اعلم انك تكرهني.
But if this kind of hate
ولكن إذا كان هذا النوع من الكراهية
Will cure you.
سوف يعالجك.
Heterosexual communication disorder
اضطراب التواصل بين الجنسين
I'd rather be hated by you.
أنا أفضل أن تكرهني.
Brother
أخ
I can't. I really want to vomit.
لا أستطبع.  أنا حقا أريد أن أتقيأ.
Go there and vomit.
اذهب هناك وتقيأ.